SHARATH THOMAS

P +919048611293

E sharathct22@gmail.com



github.com/thesct22



W sharath.is-a.dev

OBJECTIVE

Experienced in the field of Cloud Computing, DevOps, IoT, Web Development and App Development. Hardworking, sincere and have never failed to meet deadlines. Have a passion for acquiring new skills while mastering existing skills. Looking forward to working in a challenging and fast-paced work environment.

EXPERIENCE

December 2019 - August 2020

Project Intern • Samsung PRISM Project

June 2019 - July 2019

Intern • Edgate Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

LEADERSHIP

Technical Lead, International Society of Automation Student Chapter, VIT (April 2019 – April 2020)

CERTIFICATIONS

- DO081x: Fundamentals of Containers, Kubernetes, and Red Hat OpenShift • EdX
- Architecting with Google Kubernetes Engine Coursera
- Architecting with Google Compute Engine Coursera
- Cloud Engineering with Google Cloud Coursera
- Industrial IoT on Google Cloud Platform Coursera
- Introduction to Big Data Coursera

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Conference Paper, DOI: https://doi.org/10.1007/978-981-15-8221-9_16
- Journal Publication, DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.34218/ijeet.11.4.2020.046
- Won IEEE Techloop 2019, conducted in VIT, Vellore in the month of March 2019.
- Finalist in IoT Challenge 2019, conducted in IIT Bombay in March 2019.
- Finalist in iAct 2019, conducted by ISA, Bangalore in March 2019.
- Finalist in Hack Off v2.0, conducted by IET-VIT in December 2019.

EDUCATION

Vellore Institute of Technology

Vellore

B.Tech. Electronics and Communications Engineering with Spec. in IoT and Sensors

July 2017 - May 2021

CGPA: 8.9/10

KEY SKILLS

- **GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM**
- **DOCKER**
- **KUBERNETES**
- **ANDROID STUDIO**
- **MERN STACK**
- **DEVOPS**
- **GIT**

LANGUAGES

- **JAVASCRIPT**
- JAVA
- **PYTHON**
- C
- C++
- **SQL**